globalcashcard.com 2004-04-06

# :: World Processing, LTD. -- Global Cash Card :: Privacy Policy

At **World Processing, LTD.** , we recognize that privacy and security of personal financial information is a concern to our customers. We have taken the utmost care in establishing and implementing policies and procedures to protect this information.

**YOUR PRIVACY IS A PRIORITY**  
We are committed to provide products, services, and offers of value to you and your family. We may use information from our interactions with you and other customers, and from other parties, to help us achieve that goal.

Your privacy is considered in all aspects of our business. Our employees are informed of their responsibility to protect confidential customer information and are governed by a code of conduct that includes this confidentiality. Appropriate disciplinary policies are in place to help enforce employee privacy responsibilities. Security procedures and internal controls are also in place to protect our customers' privacy.

We believe that the basis of each customer relationship is trust. Because you trust us with your personal information, we are committed to respect your privacy and safeguard that information. In order to preserve that trust, we pledge to protect your privacy by adhering to practices intended to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe, secure, and responsible manner.

**WHY WE COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION**  
World Processing, LTD. receives and retains information about its customers through many sources. We limit the use and collection of this information to that which is necessary to maintain and administer financial services, provide excellent service, and offer new products and services that may be of benefit to our customers.

We gather information about you and your account so we can (a) deliver products and services to meet your needs, (b) know who you are and thereby prevent unauthorized access to your information, (c) design and improve the products we offer, (d) replace a lost card, pin, or to provide some other form of assistance, and (e) comply with laws and regulations that govern us.

**WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
We may collect the following types of "non-public personal information" about you:

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms.

  * Information about your transactions with our affiliates or us.

  * Information about your transactions with non-affiliated third parties.

**World Processing, LTD.** is committed to fully complying with the laws and regulations, such as the Fair Credit Reporting Act and the Right to Financial Privacy Act, that have been established to protect the confidentiality of customer information. If we obtain and use information from a third party such as a consumer report, we will notify you. You are entitled to request credit reporting agencies to remove your name from lists supplied to us.

**World Processing, LTD.** does exchange information about our customers to reputable information reporting agencies, in accordance with standard industry practice, to maximize the accuracy and security of such information and verify the existence and condition of customers' accounts. We do not share specific personal customer information with independent companies for any other purpose without the customer's consent, except when required by law, regulation, or court order, and to third party litigants when required by lawful judicial process or court order.

**WHAT INFORMATION WE DISCLOSE**  
We collect, use and share information about you so that we can provide the highest level of service to you for the products you use. We require companies to which we disclose non-public information about you to maintain its confidentiality.

We may share information we collect to our affiliates (i.e., companies related to us by common control or ownership) that offer financial services or additional products and services. In addition, we may disclose information we collect to companies, both affiliates and non-affiliates that perform marketing or other services on our behalf or to other companies with which we have joint marketing arrangements. We are also permitted under law to disclose non-public personal information about you to affiliates and "non-affiliated third parties" in certain circumstances. For example, we may disclose non-public personal information about you to companies that assist us in servicing your account.

In certain circumstances, in order to comply with government requirements or court orders, we are required to disclose information about you or your transactions. We will do this only when required by law, regulation or court order. We share only the information required.

**HOW TO LIMIT SOLICITATIONS**  
From time to time, we or our affiliates or partners may call or write to tell you about products or services that we think may be of interest to you. You may tell us not to market products or services to you through telemarketing or direct mail marketing and not to provide your information to our affiliates or partners for marketing purposes by submitting a "no solicitation" request. You may, however, continue to receive promotional information in account related notices or other business purpose communications, including electronic announcements.

If you choose not to receive direct mail or telephone solicitations, please write to Customer Service at 26500 West Agoura Road, Suite 102-676, Calabasas, CA 91302 and request that we do not solicit you through, or provide information about you to financial partners for telemarketing or direct mail marketing. Please include your name, address, 16-digit card number or 10-digit ID number.

**PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION ON THE INTERNET**  
We are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our privacy policy applies in its entirety to your Internet and PC transactions.

**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**  
Member Personal and Financial Information is private and passed through a highly secured state-of-the-art SSL (Secured Socket Line). Our system is a security focused that requires the leading 128-bit SSL certificates and Web sites solutions, Secure Site Services provide you with all of the authentication and encryption power.

We restrict access to non-public personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to complete transactions or to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your information.

**CLOSED OR INACTIVE ACCOUNTS**  
We will continue to adhere to the privacy policies and practices described in this notice even after your account is closed or becomes inactive.

**TO CHANGE YOUR ELECTION**  
If you would like to change a previous decision to limit direct marketing or sharing of nonpublic personal information please call the toll-free number on the back of your Card, or write us at the address listed above.

**ADDITIONAL RIGHTS AND MODIFICATIONS**  
You may have other privacy protections under state laws, and we will comply with applicable state laws when we share information about you. We may amend this privacy notice at any time, and we will inform you of changes as required by law.
